Karen Shearer Collection, 1935-1996, bulk 1974-1992
Indiana University Digital Library Program
- 1. Special Edition (radio program), 1975-1994
  - 1.2. Special Edition Radio Program Transcripts, 1975-1988
    - Johnson, Jesse, 1987 February 9, SE 87-07; 6 typed leaves
    - Johnson, Jesse, 1988 June 13, SE 88-25; 6 typed leaves
    - Jones Girls, 1981 March 7, SE 81-10; 8 typed leaves
    - Jones Girls, 1982 July 10, SE 82-27; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Jones Girls, 1983 December 24, SE 83-52; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Jones, Booker T., 1982 January 27, SE 82-08; 9 typed leaves
    - Jones, Glenn, 1987 November 23, SE 87-48; 6 typed leaves
    - Jones, Quincy, 1982 May 15, SE 82-19; 9 typed leaves + notes
    - Jones, Quincy, 1982 May 22, SE 82-20; 9 typed leaves + notes
    - Jones, Shirley & Glenn Jones, 1986 November 17, SE 86-47; 5 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1984 October 22, SE 84-44; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Kashif, 1986 January 20, SE 86-04; 8 typed leaves
    - Kashif, 1986 November 2, SE 86-45; 6 typed leaves
    - Kashif & Company, 1988 February 1, SE 88-06; 6 typed leaves
    - Kashif & Company, 1988 February 8, SE 88-07; 6 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1981 July 11, SE 81-28; 10 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1983 March 26, SE 83-13; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Khan, Chaka, 1985 January 21, SE 85-04; 8 typed leaves
    - Khan, Chaka, 1986 December 1, SE 86-49; 6 typed leaves
    - King, Ben E., 1981 October 3, SE 81-40; 9 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn Champagne, 1980 April 26, SE 80-11; 5 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn Champagne, 1983 May 21, SE 83-21; 5 typed leaves + notes
    - King, Evelyn Champagne, 1984 June 18, SE 84-26; 5 typed leaves + notes
    - King, Evelyn Champagne, 1985 November 4, SE 85-45; 6 typed leaves
    - King, Evelyn Champagne, 1988 June 20, SE 88-26; 5 typed leaves
    - Klugh, Earl, 1982 June 19, SE 82-24; 9 typed leaves + notes (Box 17)
    - Klymaxx, 1986 April 7, SE 86-15; 6 typed leaves
    - Klymaxx, 1987 March 23, SE 87-13; 6 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1982 January 30, SE 82-05; 8 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1983 July 23, SE 83-30; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1983 July 30, SE 83-31; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1985 May 13, SE 85-20; 8 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1985 May 20, SE 85-21; 8 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1987 April 20, SE 87-17; 8 typed leaves
    - Knight, Gladys & The Pips, 1988 February 15, SE 88-08; 7 typed leaves
    - Kool & the Gang, 1981 November 28, SE 81-48; 7 typed leaves
    - LTD, 1980 November 8, SE 80-39; 12 typed leaves
    - LTD, 1982 July 3, SE 82-26; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1984 March 12, SE 84-12; 7 typed leaves
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1985 June 17, SE 85-25; 8 typed leaves
    - LaBelle, Patti, 1986 July 14, SE 86-29; 7 typed leaves
    - Lakeside, 1982 May 1, SE 82-17; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Lakeside, 1984 October 29, SE 84-45; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Lakeside, 1987 August 24, SE 87-35; 5 typed leaves
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1984 June 4, SE 84-24; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1987 January 12, SE 87-03; 7 typed leaves
    - Lattisaw, Stacy, 1988 May 23, SE 88-22; 6 typed leaves
    - Laws, Ronnie, 1982 April 10, SE 82-15; 7 typed leaves
    - Laws, Ronnie, 1989 November 5, SE 83-45; 8 typed leaves
    - Levert & The Jets, 1987 April 13, SE 87-16; 6 typed leaves
    - Levert, 1988 May 16, SE 88-21; 6 typed leaves
    - Lisa Lisa & Cult Jam with Full Force, 1987 August 10, SE 87-33; 6 typed leaves
    - Little Richard, 1984 December 17, SE 84-52; 10 typed leaves
    - Live from the Apollo, 1985 December 16, [unnumbered]; 5 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1982 October 2, SE 82-39; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1984 February 27, SE 84-10; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1985 September 23, SE 85-39; 7 typed leaves
    - Lynn, Cheryl, 1987 October 22, SE 87-42; 5 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1980 September 27, SE 80-33; 15 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1983 April 30, SE 83-18; 4 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1985 July 22, SE 85-30; 6 typed leaves
    - Manhattans, 1987 March 9, SE 87-11; 7 typed leaves
    - Maze, 1985 July 8, SE 85-28; 7 typed leaves
    - Maze, 1986 December 15, SE 86-51; 7 typed leaves
    - McFadden & Whitehead, 1981 January 3, SE 81-01; 9 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1984 April 2, SE 84-15; 6 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1985 June 10, SE 85-24; 5 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1986 September 1, SE 86-36; 6 typed leaves
    - Midnight Star, 1988 December 5, SE 88-50; 6 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1981 December 26, SE 81-52; 7 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1983 January 8, SE 83-02; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Moore, Melba, 1984 April 9, SE 84-16; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Moore, Melba, 1985 July 29, SE 85-31; 8 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1986 October 20, SE 86-43; 6 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1987 August 3, SE 87-32; 6 typed leaves
    - Moore, Melba, 1988 November 7, SE 88-46; 6 typed leaves
    - Morgan, Meli'sa, & Joyce Sims, 1988 April 18, SE 88-17; 6 typed leaves
    - Mtume, 1986 October 13, SE 86-42; 6 typed leaves
    - Murdock, Shirley, & Bobby Brown, 1988 October 10, SE 88-42; 3 typed leaves
    - New Edition, 1985 August 26, SE 85-35; 7 typed leaves
    - New Edition, 1986 September 29, SE 86-40; 7 typed leaves
    - New Edition, 1988 August 29, SE 88-36; 6 typed leaves
    - Ocean, Billy, 1985 December 16, SE 85-51; 7 typed leaves (Box 18)
    - Ocean, Billy, 1986 August 4, SE 86-32; 5 typed leaves
    - Ocean, Billy, 1988 May 30, SE 88-23; 7 typed leaves
    - Ocean, Billy, 1988 December 12, SE 88-51; 7 typed leaves
    - Ohio Players, 1981 August 15, SE 81-33; 9 typed leaves
    - O'Jays, 1982 October 16, SE 82-41; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - O'Jays, 1982 October 16, SE 82-42; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - O'Jays, 1984 October 1, SE 84-41; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - O'Jays, 1984 October 8, SE 84-42; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - O'Jays, 1986 February 17, SE 86-08; 8 typed leaves
    - O'Jays, 1986 February 24, SE 86-09; 7 typed leaves
    - O'Jays, 1986 November 2, SE 87-45; 7 typed leaves
    - O'Jays, 1987 November 9, SE 87-46; 6 typed leaves + commercial assignment sheet
    - One Way, 1982 July 24, SE 82-29; 6 typed leaves
    - One Way, 1983 November 12, SE 83-46; 8 typed leaves
    - One Way, 1984 October 15, SE 84-43; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - O'Neal, Alexander & Cherelle, 1986 September 8, SE 86-37; 7 typed leaves
    - O'Neal, Alexander, 1987 October 5, SE 87-41; 5 typed leaves
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, 1983 October 8, SE 83-41; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, 1985 August 19, SE 85-34; 7 typed leaves
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, 1986 August 18, SE 86-34; 6 typed leaves
    - Osborne, Jeffrey, 1983 October 24, SE 88-44; 6 typed leaves
    - Parker, Ray, Jr. & Raydio, 1980 July 12, SE 80-22; 7 typed leaves
    - Parker, Ray & Raydio, 1981 October 17, SE 81-42; 8 typed leaves
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1982 October 9, SE 82-40; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1984 February 6, SE 84-07; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1984 February 13, SE 84-08; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1986 December 30, SE 86-01; 7 typed leaves
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1985 January 6, SE 86-02; 6 typed leaves
    - Parker, Jr., Ray, 1987 December 7, SE 87-50; 6 typed leaves
    - Parliament Funkadelic, 1981 April 18, SE 81-16; 8 typed leaves
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1981 December 12, SE 81-50; 7 typed leaves
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1984 August 27, SE 84-36; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1984 September 3, SE 84-37; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1988 August 8, SE 88-33; 6 typed leaves
    - Pendergrass, Teddy, 1988 August 15, SE 88-34; 6 typed leaves
    - Phillips, Esther, 1981 June 13, SE 81-24; 9 typed leaves
    - Pointer Sisters, 1983 November 26, SE 83-48; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Pointer Sisters, 1983 December 3, SE 83-49; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Pointer Sister. Chevy Super Tour, 1986 January, [unnumbered]; 12 typed leaves + annotated copies
    - Pointer Sisters, 1986 May 12, SE 86-20; 7 typed leaves
    - Pointer Sisters, 1986 May 19, SE 86-21; 7 typed leaves
    - Pointer Sisters, 1987 February 16, SE 87-08; 6 typed leaves
    - Preston, Billy, 1981 October 31, SE 81-44; 7 typed leaves
    - Rawls, Lou, 1983 June 18, SE 83-25; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Ray, Goodman & Brown (& Rose Royce), 1987 March 16, SE 87-12; 7 typed leaves
    - Ready for the World, 1987 May 11, SE 87-20; 7 typed leaves
    - Ready for the World, 1988 November 21, SE 88-48; 5 typed leaves
    - Reddings, 1982 July 23, SE 82-32; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Rene & Angela, 1986 August 25, SE 86-35; 6 typed leaves
    - Ritchie, Lionel, 1983 February 12, SE 83-06; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1981 June 20, SE 81-25; 11 typed leaves + notes (Box 19)
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1989 May 7, SE 83-19; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1983 May 14, SE 83-20; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1986 April 14, SE 86-16; 7 typed leaves
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1986 April 21, SE 86-17; 5 typed leaves
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1987 May 25, SE 87-22; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Robinson, Smokey, 1987 June 1, SE 87-23; 6 typed leaves
    - Rodgers, Nile, 1985 September 30, SE 85-40; 7 typed leaves
    - Rose Royce, 1981 January 31, SE 81-05; 10 typed leaves
    - Rufus, undated, SE ??; 5 typed leaves
    - Rufus, 1983 June 11, SE 83-24; 6 typed leaves + alternate version (7 pages), notes
    - Run D.M.C./Whodini, 1986 July 21, SE 86-30; 8 typed leaves
    - Run D.M.C., 1988 July 25, SE 88-30; 6 typed leaves
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1980 December 20, SE 80-45; 7 typed leaves
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1982 June 26, SE 82-25; 9 typed leaves + notes
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1984 August 13, SE 84-33; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1984 August 13, SE 84-34; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Rushen, Patrice, 1987 June 15, SE 87-25; 6 typed leaves
    - Russell, Brenda, 1981 June 27, SE 81-26; 15 typed leaves
    - Russell, Brenda, 1988 July 4, SE 88-28; 6 typed leaves
    - S.O.S. Band, 1983 October 29, SE 83-44; 6 typed leaves
    - Sade, 1986 March 31, SE 86-14; 8 typed leaves
    - Shalamar, undated, [unnumbered]; 9 typed leaves
    - Shalamar, featuring Jody Watley, 1988 January 18, SE 88-04; 6 typed leaves
    - Side Effect, 1981 July 25, SE 81-30; 12 typed leaves
    - Simon, Joe, 1981 August 1, SE 81-31; 10 typed leaves
    - Sister Sledge, 1981 February 7, SE 81-06; 8 typed leaves
    - Sister Sledge, 1982 May 8, SE 82-18; 7 typed leaves + notes (2 pages)
    - Sister Sledge, 1983 August 6, SE 83-32; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Skyy, 1982 December 4, SE 82-48; 5 typed leaves + notes
    - Slave, 1982 February 13, SE 82-07; 7 typed leaves
    - Spinners, 1982 March 13, SE 82-11; 8 typed leaves
    - Spinners, 1983 February 19, SE 83-8; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Spinners, 1984 September 17, SE 84-39; 7 typed leaves
    - Staple Singers, 1985 April 8, SE 85-15; 8 typed leaves
    - Starpoint, 1986 March 10, SE 86-11; 7 typed leaves
    - Starpoint, 1987 May 18, SE 87-21; 6 typed leaves
    - Staton, Candi, 1981 October 10, SE 81-41; 8 typed leaves
    - Summer, Donna, 1982 September 4, SE 82-35; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Summer, Donna, 1982 September 11, SE 82-36; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Sylvers, 1980 September 29, SE 80-42; 7 typed leaves
    - Sylvers, Leon, 1983 March 12, SE 83-11; 6 typed leaves + interview notes (2 pages)
    - Syreeta, 1981 November 7, SE 81-45; 7 typed leaves
    - System, 1987 July 20, SE 87-30; 6 typed leaves
    - Taste of Honey, 1981 March 21, SE 81-12; 10 typed leaves
    - Taste of Honey, 1982 September 18, SE 82-37; 7 typed leaves + notes (2 pages)
    - Tavares, undated, [unnumbered]; 15 typed leaves
    - Tavares, 1981 January 17, SE 81-03; 9 typed leaves
    - Tavares, 1982 November 27, SE 82-47; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Tavares, 1984 January 23, SE 84-05; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Taylor, Johnny, 1981 October 24, SE 81-43; 8 typed leaves
    - Teena Marie, 1981 September 26, SE 81-39; 6 typed leaves (Box 20)
    - Teena Marie, 1984 January 9, SE 84-03; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Teena Marie, 1985 February 25, SE 85-09; 7 typed leaves
    - Teena Marie, 1986 September 15, SE 86-38; 6 typed leaves
    - Teena Marie, 1988 August 12, SE 88-40; 8 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1982 June 5, SE 82-22; 8 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1982 June 12, SE 82-23; 9 typed leaves + notes
    - Temptations, 1985 March 18, SE 85-12; 8 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1985 March 25, SE 85-13; 8 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1986 March 17, SE 86-12; 7 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1986 March 24, SE 86-13; 7 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1988 February 29, SE 88-10; 7 typed leaves
    - Temptations, 1988 March 7, SE 88-11; 6 typed leaves
    - Thomas, Lillo & Gregory Abbott, 1987 July 27, SE 87-31; 6 typed leaves
    - Thomas, Lillo, 1988 March 21, SE 88-13; 5 typed leaves
    - Time, 1982 December 18, SE 82-50; 5 typed leaves + notes
    - Turner, Tina, 1984 September 24, SE 84-40; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Vandross, Luther, 1982 January 2, SE 82-01; 7 typed leaves
    - Vandross, Luther, 1983 January 1, SE 83-1; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Vandross, Luther, 1985 April 29, SE 85-18; 7 typed leaves
    - Vandross, Luther, 1986 December 8, SE 86-50; 6 typed leaves
    - Vandross, Luther, 1987 September 21, SE 87-39; 5 typed leaves
    - Vandross, Luther, 1988 November 28, SE 88-49; 6 typed leaves
    - Walden, Narada Michael, 1982 August 31, SE 82-33; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Walden, Narada Michael, 1983 September 3, SE 83-36; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Walden, Narada Michael, 1988 July 11, SE 88-29; 6 typed leaves
    - War, 1982 July 17, SE 82-28; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Warwick, Dionne, undated, [unnumbered]; 7 typed leaves
    - Warwick, Dionne, 1983 February 26, SE 83-9; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Warwick, Dionne, 1984 April 16, SE 84-17; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - Warwick, Dionne, 1986 June 16, SE 86-25; 7 typed leaves
    - Warwick, Dionne, 1987 November 30, SE 87-49; 6 typed leaves
    - Washington, Grover, 1981 May 30, SE 81-22; 9 typed leaves + notes
    - Watley, Jody, 1987 July 6, SE 87-28; 7 typed leaves
    - Watley, Jody, 1988 September 5, SE 88-37; 7 typed leaves
    - Whispers, 1982 April 3, SE 82-14; 8 typed leaves
    - Whispers, 1983 May 28, SE 83-22; 5 typed leaves + notes
    - Whispers, 1985 May 6, SE 85-19; 7 typed leaves
    - Whispers, 1987 June 29, SE 87-27; 6 typed leaves
    - White, Barry, 1982 November 6, SE 82-44; 7 typed leaves + notes
    - White, Barry, 1988 April 11, SE 88-16; 6 typed leaves
    - White, Lennie, 1981 January 10, SE 81-02; 10 typed leaves
    - White, Maurice, 1985 December 2, SE 85-48; 8 typed leaves
    - White, Maurice, 1985 December 2, SE 85-49; 7 typed leaves
    - Wilde, Eugene. Live from the Apollo, undated, [unnumbered]; 3 typed leaves
    - Wilde, Eugene, 1986 February 10, SE 86-07; 7 typed leaves
    - Williams, Deniece, 1981 June 6, SE 81-23; 11 typed leaves
    - Williams, Deniece, 1982 November 13, SE 82-45; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Williams, Deniece, 1983 November 19, SE 83-47; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Williams, Deniece, 1984 November 5, SE 84-46; 7 typed leaves
    - Williams, Deniece, 1987 July 13, SE 87-29; 8 typed leaves
    - Williams, Deniece, 1988 December 19, SE 88-52; 6 typed leaves
    - Williams, James "D" Train & Howard Hewitt,, 1987 January 26, SE 87-05; 8 typed leaves
    - Wilson, Nancy, undated, [unnumbered]; 13 typed leaves
    - Wilson, Nancy, 1981 May 2, SE 81-18; 11 typed leaves
    - Withers, Bill, 1985 August 2, SE 85-36; 7 typed leaves
    - Womack, Bobby, 1981 December 19, SE 81-51; 9 typed leaves
    - Womack, Bobby, 1984 June 25, SE 84-27; 8 typed leaves + notes
    - Womack, Bobby, 1985 November 18, SE 85-47; 8 typed leaves
    - Wonder, Stevie. Showtime special, 1984 June 18, [unnumbered]; 8 typed leaves + interview notes (2 pages)
    - Wonder, Stevie, 1984 December 31, SE 85-01; 9 typed leaves
    - Yarbrough & Peoples, 1986 June 9, SE 86-24; 5 typed leaves
    - Zapp, 1982 November 20, SE 82-46; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Zapp, 1983 October 22, SE 83-43; 6 typed leaves + notes
    - Zapp & Roger, 1988 February 22, SE 88-09; 6 typed leaves
  - 1.3. Special Edition Artist Publicity Materials, 1979-1994
    - 101 North (Musical group) (Box 21)
    - 2 Deep (Musical group)
    - 3rd Bass (Musical group)
    - 4 by Four (Musical group)
    - 52nd Street (Musical group)
    - 7A3 (Musical group)
    - 9.9 (Musical group)
    - Abbott, Gregory
    - Abdul, Paula
    - Above the Law (Musical group)
    - Abrams, Colonel
    - Absolute (Musical group)
    - Adams, Oleta
    - Adeva
    - Afrika Bambaataa, 1960-
    - Alexander, JW
    - Alfie
    - Allen, Debbie
    - Alston, Gerald
    - Anderson, Carl
    - Anderson, Ernestine
    - Anthony & The Camp (Musical group)
    - Apollonia
    - Armatrading, Joan
    - Arrington, Steve
    - Ashford & Simpson
    - Atlantic Starr (Musical group)
    - Austin, Patti
    - Avila, Bobby Ross
    - Aweke, Aster
    - Ayers, Roy
    - B Angie B (Musician)
    - Babyface (Musician)
    - Bad Manners (Musical group)
    - Badarou, Wally
    - Bailey, Phillip
    - Baker, Anita
    - Banton, Pato
    - Bar-Kays (Musical group)
    - Basic Black (Musical group)
    - Battle, Hinton
    - Beasley, Walter
    - Beastie Boys
    - Beatmasters (Musical group)
    - Beauvoir, Jean
    - Belafonte, Harry
    - Bell Biv DeVoe (Musical group)
    - Bell, Margaret
    - Belle, Regina
    - Benson, George
    - Berkeley, Tyrone
    - Berry, Chuck
    - B-Fats (Musician)
    - Biscuit
    - Biz Markie, 1964-
    - Blake & Hines
    - Blanchard, Terence
    - Bland, Bobby
    - Blaze (Musical group)
    - Bleu, Mikki
    - Blondy, Alpha, 1953-
    - Blow, Kurtis
    - Blu, Peggi (Box 22)
    - Blue Magic (Musical group)
    - Blue Pearl
    - Blythe, Arthur
    - Body (Musical group)
    - Bofill, Angela
    - Bohannon, Hamilton
    - Boo, Betty
    - Boogie Boys
    - Boys (Musical group)
    - Boyz II Men (Musical group)
    - Brand New Heavies (Musical group)
    - Brand Nubian (Musical group)
    - Brazil Classics 1 (Title)
    - Breakfast Club (Musical group)
    - Bridgewater, Dee Dee
    - Bristol, Johnny
    - Brookins, Robert
    - Brothers Johnson (Musical group)
    - Brown, Bobby, vocalist
    - Brown, James
    - Brown, Jocelyn
    - Browne, Tom
    - Brownmark (Musician)
    - Brunson, Tyrone
    - Bryson, Peabo
    - Burton, Jenny
    - Bus Boys (Musical group)
    - Busy Bee (Musical group)
    - Butcher, Jon
    - Butler, Jerry
    - Butler, Jonathan
    - Cabo Frio (Musical group)
    - Cameron (Musical group)
    - Campbell, Stan
    - Campbell, Tevin
    - Cara, Irene
    - Carey, Mariah
    - Carlton, Carl
    - Carman, Pauli
    - Carn, Jean
    - Carter, Clarence
    - Champaign (Musical group)
    - Channel 2 (Musical group)
    - Chapman, Tracy
    - Chapter 8 (Musical group)
    - Charles & Eddie
    - Charles, Ray, 1930-
    - Charvoni
    - Cherrelle
    - Cherry, Ava
    - Cherry, Neneh
    - Chi-Lites
    - Chill Factor (Musical group)
    - Chimes (Musical group)
    - Christopher, Gavin
    - Cinema (Musical group)
    - Clarke, Stanley
    - Clarke, Stanley; Duke, George
    - Clegg, Johnny, 1953-; Savuka (Musical group)
    - Clemons, Clarence
    - Cliff, Jimmy
    - Clinton, George (Box 23)
    - Club Nouveau (Musical group)
    - Cole, Gardner
    - Cole, Nat King, 1917-1965
    - Cole, Natalie, 1950-
    - Collage (Musical group)
    - Collins, Bootsy
    - Commodores (Musical group)
    - Con Funk Shun (Musical group)
    - Connors, Norman
    - Controllers (Musical group)
    - Cooke, Sam
    - Cooper, Michael
    - Cover Girls (Musical group)
    - Crawford, Randy
    - Cray, Robert
    - Crouch, Andraé
    - Crusaders (Musical group)
    - Cymone, Andre
    - Cyrille, Andrew
    - D Train (Musical group)
    - D.J. Jazzy Jeff
    - Dá Krash (Musical group)
    - Daim, Lushus
    - Dame, Damian
    - Dane, Dana
    - Daniel, Jeffrey
    - D'Arby, Terence Trent, 1962-
    - Dash, Sarah
    - Davis, Carole
    - Davis, Don
    - Davis, Miles
    - Davis, Rainy
    - Davy D.
    - Day, Morris
    - Dayne, Taylor
    - Dazz Band
    - DeBarge (Musical group)
    - Dee, Mark
    - Deele (Musical group)
    - Def Con 4 (Musical group)
    - DeFrancesco, Joey
    - DeJohnette, Jack
    - Dells (Musical group)
    - Des'ree (Box 24)
    - DiMeola, Al
    - Dirty Dozen Brass Band
    - Dixon, Willie
    - Djavan, 1949-
    - Doc Box & B. Fresh (Musical group)
    - Dorsey, Gail
    - Dorsey, Thomas
    - Dramatics
    - D'Rivera, Paquito, 1948-
    - Dulfer, Candy
    - Dyer, Ian
    - E., Sheila (Escovedo), 1959-
    - Earth, Wind & Fire (Musical group)
    - Edwards, Dennis
    - Emotions (Musical group)
    - En Vogue (Musical group)
    - England, Colin
    - Esquerita
    - Estus, Deon
    - Everyday People (Musical group)
    - Exposé (Musical group)
    - Fassie, Brenda
    - Fat Boys (Musical group)
    - Fela, 1938-
    - Felder, Wilton
    - Fields, Richard
    - Fischer, André
    - Fishbone (Musical group)
    - Fit (Musical group)
    - Five Star (Musical group)
    - Flack, Roberta
    - Force MD's (Musical group)
    - Ford, Penny
    - Foster, Ian
    - Four Tops
    - Foxxx, Freddie
    - Franklin, Aretha
    - Freelon, Nnenna
    - Full Force (Musical group)
    - Gable, Eric
    - Gap Band
    - Garrett, Siedah
    - Gatling, Jimmy
    - Gaye, Marvin
    - General Caine (Musical group) (Box 25)
    - General Kane (Musical group)
    - Genius (Musician)
    - Georgio
    - Gilbert, Derrick I. M.
    - Gill, Johnny
    - Glover, Bobby
    - Good Girls (Musical group)
    - Good Question (Musical group)
    - Grandmaster Flash
    - Grant, Eddy
    - Gray, Dobie
    - Guesss (Musical group)
    - Guinn (Musical group)
    - Gumbs, Onaje Allan, 1949-
    - Guthrie, Gwen
    - Guy Called Gerald, 1967-
    - Guy, Jasmine
    - Gyrlz (Musical group)
    - Hall, Erasmus
    - Hall, Randy
    - Hammer, M. C., 1963-
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1940-
    - Harrell, Grady
    - Harris, Hugh
    - Harrison, Donald; Blanchard, Terence
    - Havens, Richie
    - Hayes, Isaac
    - Heavy D. & the Boyz (Musical group)
    - Hendrix, Jimi
    - Hendryx, Nona
    - Hewitt, Howard
    - Hicks, D'Atra
    - Holland-Dozier-Holland
    - Holliday, Jennifer
    - Hollywood Beyond (Musical group)
    - Homework (Musical group)
    - Hooker, John Lee
    - Hopkins, Linda
    - Houston, Thelma
    - Houston, Whitney
    - Howard, George, 1956-
    - Howard, Miki
    - Hudson, Al; One Way (Musical group)
    - Hunter, Alberta
    - Huntsberry, Howard
    - Hutch, Willie
    - Hyman, Phyllis
    - Ice Cream Tee (Musician)
    - Ice-T (Musician)
    - Icy Blu (Musician)
    - Incorporated Thang Band (Box 26)
    - Ingram, James
    - Irby, Joyce
    - Isley Brothers
    - Jackson, Freddie
    - Jackson, Janet, 1966-
    - Jackson, Jermaine
    - Jackson, Keisha
    - Jackson, La Toya
    - Jackson, Marlon
    - Jackson, Michael, 1958-
    - Jackson, Millie
    - Jackson, Milt
    - Jackson, Rebbie
    - Jade, musician
    - Jam, Jimmy & Terry Lewis
    - Jamaica Boys (Musical group)
    - Jamal, Ahmad, 1930-
    - Jamerson, James, 1936-1983
    - James, Rick, 1948-; Stone City Band
    - Jamiroquai (Musical group)
    - Jarreau, Al
    - Jeffries, Michael
    - Jenkins, Tomi
    - Jets
    - Johnson, Henry
    - Johnson, Howard
    - Johnson, Jesse
    - Johnson, Robert
    - Johnson, Troy
    - Jones Girls (Musical group) (Box 27)
    - Jones, Booker T.
    - Jones, Glenn
    - Jones, Grace